<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Parakram\'24</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="About_IIT_ISM">
        "The Indian Institute of Technology (Indian School of Mines), i.e., IIT (ISM), is a premier engineering and research institution located in the heart of the mineral-rich region of India in the city of Dhanbad. Founded in 1926 as Indian School of Mines, the institute is on the verge of completing its centenary year of establishment. It has the privilege of being recognized as the Institute of National Importance under the Institutes of Technology Act, 1961. This third oldest institute among the IITs stood envisioned to be a State of Art educational and research destination for earth sciences and engineering in India. With this legacy, it has witnessed exponential growth and expansion in various technical domains besides earth sciences. Recently, the institute featured at 25th rank in the QS World University Rankings of 2023 in the field of Mining and Mineral Engineering. The IIT (ISM) admits its undergraduate students through the Joint Entrance Examination (Advanced). The institute has 18 academic departments covering Engineering, Applied Sciences, Humanities and Social Sciences, and Management studies."
    </string>
    <string name="convenersMessage">
        " The combination of talent, hard effort, compassion, competitive spirit, and enthusiasm is what makes sports great. It is the one thing that, regardless of gender, age, color, religion, caste, or anything else, can unite the entire globe in a state of innocent surprise and delight. Without a strong sports culture, I think education is still incomplete since healthy growth benefits everyone—individuals as well as society at large. Sports are the only activities that combine work with delight, anger with serenity, and brotherhood with rivalry. As we at IIT(ISM), Dhanbad are proud of India's multifarious sports culture, we are pleased to announce the creation of 'Parakram '24', the most opulent annual sports gathering in East India, in honor of it. The three day annual sports festival strives to showcase the sportsmanship in every individual and make them realize their true potential ,rebrand the culture of sports and gaming that is unfortunately often looked down upon in our country. “In the symphony of life, sports provide the rhythm, the discipline, and the harmony that elevate us to the highest notes of achievement.”

The goal of ''Parakram'24'' is to provide an equitable and level playing field where all individuals and teams can showcase their full potential, both mentally and physically. As a team, we extend our warmest greetings and look forward to having you visit us at IIT (ISM), Winning or losing is a part of the game,the only thing that matters is that whether you give your best or not. “To be a champ you have to believe in yourself when no one else will”"

    </string>
    <string name="parakram">Parakram is the Annual Inter-College Sports Festival of IIT(ISM) Dhanbad. The 3-day Sports Festival of IIT(ISM) DHANBAD is one of the largest sporting fest in Eastern India. ”Parakram” in Sanskrit means efforts, strength, and heroism. Teams from various colleges compete to be the best and to lift the most aspired trophy of PARAKRAM. In the true sense, it is an exhibition of sporting fervour, and the success of the meet has been ratified by the success of many of its winners higher up in the sporting hierarchy.</string>
</resources>